import { DialogueQuestion } from '@/types/quiz';
import { addGrammarName } from '@/lib/quiz/helpers';
// 책상, 의자, 책, 휴지, 안경, 노트북, 물, 커피, 침대, 핸드폰,
// 언니, 친구, 엄마, 아빠, 오빠,
// 라면, 우유, 맥주, 사과, 바나나, 포도
// 교실, 학교, 도서관, 화장실, 집, 회사, 식당, 카페, 병원, 영화관

const questions: Omit<DialogueQuestion, 'grammarName'>[] = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: '교실에 뭐가 있어요?',
    questionTranslation: 'What is there in the classroom?',
    answer: '교실에 책상이 있어요.',
    alternativeAnswers: ['책상이 교실에 있어요.'],
    answerTranslation: 'There are desks in the classroom.',    items: [
      { id: '1', content: '책상', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '2', content: '이', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '3', content: '교실', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '4', content: '에', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '5', content: '있어요.' },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: '학교에 뭐가 있어요?',
    questionTranslation: 'What is there in the school?',
    answer: '의자가 학교에 있어요.',
    alternativeAnswers: ['학교에 의자가 있어요.'],
    answerTranslation: 'There are chairs in the school.',    items: [
      { id: '1', content: '의자', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '2', content: '가', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '3', content: '학교', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '4', content: '에', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '5', content: '있어요.' },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: '도서관에 뭐가 있어요?',
    questionTranslation: 'What is there in the library?',
    answer: '책이 도서관에 있어요.',
    alternativeAnswers: ['도서관에 책이 있어요.'],
    answerTranslation: 'There are books in the library.',    items: [
      { id: '1', content: '책', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '2', content: '이', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '3', content: '도서관', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '4', content: '에', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '5', content: '있어요.' },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: '화장실에 뭐가 있어요?',
    questionTranslation: 'What is there in the bathroom?',
    answer: '휴지가 화장실에 있어요.',
    alternativeAnswers: ['화장실에 휴지가 있어요.'],
    answerTranslation: 'There is tissue in the bathroom.',    items: [
      { id: '1', content: '휴지', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '2', content: '가', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '3', content: '화장실', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '4', content: '에', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '5', content: '있어요.' },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: '집에 뭐가 있어요?',
    questionTranslation: 'What is there in the house?',
    answer: '안경이 집에 있어요.',
    alternativeAnswers: ['집에 안경이 있어요.'],
    answerTranslation: 'There are glasses in the house.',    items: [
      { id: '1', content: '안경', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '2', content: '이', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '3', content: '집', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '4', content: '에', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '5', content: '있어요.' },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: '회사에 뭐가 있어요?',
    questionTranslation: 'What is there in the company?',
    answer: '노트북이 회사에 있어요.',
    alternativeAnswers: ['회사에 노트북이 있어요.'],
    answerTranslation: 'There is a laptop in the company.',    items: [
      { id: '1', content: '노트북', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '2', content: '이', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '3', content: '회사', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '4', content: '에', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '5', content: '있어요.' },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: '식당에 뭐가 있어요?',
    questionTranslation: 'What is there in the restaurant?',
    answer: '물이 식당에 있어요.',
    alternativeAnswers: ['식당에 물이 있어요.'],
    answerTranslation: 'There is water in the restaurant.',    items: [
      { id: '1', content: '물', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '2', content: '이', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '3', content: '식당', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '4', content: '에', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '5', content: '있어요.' },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: '카페에 뭐가 있어요?',
    questionTranslation: 'What is there in the cafe?',
    answer: '커피가 카페에 있어요.',
    alternativeAnswers: ['카페에 커피가 있어요.'],
    answerTranslation: 'There is coffee in the cafe.',    items: [
      { id: '1', content: '커피', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '2', content: '가', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '3', content: '카페', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '4', content: '에', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '5', content: '있어요.' },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: '병원에 뭐가 있어요?',
    questionTranslation: 'What is there in the hospital?',
    answer: '침대가 병원에 있어요.',
    alternativeAnswers: ['병원에 침대가 있어요.'],
    answerTranslation: 'There are beds in the hospital.',    items: [
      { id: '1', content: '침대', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '2', content: '가', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '3', content: '병원', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '4', content: '에', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '5', content: '있어요.' },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: '영화관에 뭐가 있어요?',
    questionTranslation: 'What is there in the movie theater?',
    answer: '제 핸드폰이 영화관에 있어요.',
    alternativeAnswers: ['영화관에 제 핸드폰이 있어요.'],
    answerTranslation: 'My phone is in the movie theater.',    items: [
      { id: '1', content: '제', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '2', content: '핸드폰', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '3', content: '이', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '4', content: '영화관', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '5', content: '에', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '6', content: '있어요.' },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    question: '교실에 책상이 있어요?',
    questionTranslation: 'Are there desks in the classroom?',
    answer: '책상이 교실에 없어요.',
    alternativeAnswers: ['교실에 책상이 없어요.'],
    answerTranslation: 'There are no desks in the classroom.',    items: [
      { id: '1', content: '책상', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '2', content: '이', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '3', content: '교실', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '4', content: '에', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '5', content: '없어요.' },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    question: '학교에 의자가 있어요?',
    questionTranslation: 'Are there chairs in the school?',
    answer: '의자가 학교에 없어요.',
    alternativeAnswers: ['학교에 의자가 없어요.'],
    answerTranslation: 'There are no chairs in the school.',    items: [
      { id: '1', content: '의자', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '2', content: '가', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '3', content: '학교', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '4', content: '에', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '5', content: '없어요.' },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    question: '도서관에 책이 있어요?',
    questionTranslation: 'Are there books in the library?',
    answer: '책이 도서관에 없어요.',
    alternativeAnswers: ['도서관에 책이 없어요.'],
    answerTranslation: 'There are no books in the library.',    items: [
      { id: '1', content: '책', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '2', content: '이', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '3', content: '도서관', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '4', content: '에', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '5', content: '없어요.' },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 14,
    question: '화장실에 휴지가 있어요?',
    questionTranslation: 'Is there tissue in the bathroom?',
    answer: '휴지가 화장실에 없어요.',
    alternativeAnswers: ['화장실에 휴지가 없어요.'],
    answerTranslation: 'There is no tissue in the bathroom.',    items: [
      { id: '1', content: '휴지', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '2', content: '가', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '3', content: '화장실', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '4', content: '에', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '5', content: '없어요.' },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 15,
    question: '집에 안경이 있어요?',
    questionTranslation: 'Are there glasses in the house?',
    answer: '안경이 집에 없어요.',
    alternativeAnswers: ['집에 안경이 없어요.'],
    answerTranslation: 'There are no glasses in the house.',    items: [
      { id: '1', content: '안경', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '2', content: '이', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '3', content: '집', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '4', content: '에', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '5', content: '없어요.' },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 16,
    question: '회사에 노트북이 있어요?',
    questionTranslation: 'Is there a laptop in the company?',
    answer: '노트북이 회사에 없어요.',
    alternativeAnswers: ['회사에 노트북이 없어요.'],
    answerTranslation: 'There is no laptop in the company.',    items: [
      { id: '1', content: '노트북', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '2', content: '이', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '3', content: '회사', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '4', content: '에', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '5', content: '없어요.' },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 17,
    question: '식당에 물이 있어요?',
    questionTranslation: 'Is there water in the restaurant?',
    answer: '물이 식당에 없어요.',
    alternativeAnswers: ['식당에 물이 없어요.'],
    answerTranslation: 'There is no water in the restaurant.',    items: [
      { id: '1', content: '물', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '2', content: '이', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '3', content: '식당', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '4', content: '에', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '5', content: '없어요.' },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 18,
    question: '카페에 커피가 있어요?',
    questionTranslation: 'Is there coffee in the cafe?',
    answer: '커피가 카페에 없어요.',
    alternativeAnswers: ['카페에 커피가 없어요.'],
    answerTranslation: 'There is no coffee in the cafe.',    items: [
      { id: '1', content: '커피', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '2', content: '가', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '3', content: '카페', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '4', content: '에', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '5', content: '없어요.' },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 19,
    question: '병원에 침대가 있어요?',
    questionTranslation: 'Are there beds in the hospital?',
    answer: '침대가 병원에 없어요.',
    alternativeAnswers: ['병원에 침대가 없어요.'],
    answerTranslation: 'There are no beds in the hospital.',    items: [
      { id: '1', content: '침대', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '2', content: '가', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '3', content: '병원', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '4', content: '에', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '5', content: '없어요.' },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 20,
    question: '영화관에 제 핸드폰이 있어요?',
    questionTranslation: 'Is my phone in the movie theater?',
    answer: '제 핸드폰이 영화관에 없어요.',
    alternativeAnswers: ['영화관에 제 핸드폰이 없어요.'],
    answerTranslation: 'My phone is not in the movie theater.',    items: [
      { id: '1', content: '제', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '2', content: '핸드폰', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '3', content: '이', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '4', content: '영화관', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '5', content: '에', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '6', content: '없어요.' },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 21,
    question: '교실에 누가 있어요?',
    questionTranslation: 'Who is in the classroom?',
    answer: '선생님이 교실에 있어요.',
    alternativeAnswers: ['교실에 선생님이 있어요.'],
    answerTranslation: 'A teacher is in the classroom.',    items: [
      { id: '1', content: '선생님', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '2', content: '이', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '3', content: '교실', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '4', content: '에', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '5', content: '있어요.' },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 22,
    question: '학교에 누가 있어요?',
    questionTranslation: 'Who is in school?',
    answer: '학생이 학교에 있어요.',
    alternativeAnswers: ['학교에 학생이 있어요.'],
    answerTranslation: 'Students are in school.',    items: [
      { id: '1', content: '학생', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '2', content: '이', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '3', content: '학교', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '4', content: '에', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '5', content: '있어요.' },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 23,
    question: '도서관에 누가 있어요?',
    questionTranslation: 'Who is in the library?',
    answer: '언니가 도서관에 있어요.',
    alternativeAnswers: ['도서관에 언니가 있어요.'],
    answerTranslation: 'My sister is in the library.',    items: [
      { id: '1', content: '언니', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '2', content: '가', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '3', content: '도서관', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '4', content: '에', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '5', content: '있어요.' },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 24,
    question: '화장실에 누가 있어요?',
    questionTranslation: 'Who is in the bathroom?',
    answer: '친구가 화장실에 있어요.',
    alternativeAnswers: ['화장실에 친구가 있어요.'],
    answerTranslation: 'My friend is in the bathroom.',    items: [
      { id: '1', content: '친구', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '2', content: '가', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '3', content: '화장실', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '4', content: '에', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '5', content: '있어요.' },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 25,
    question: '집에 누가 있어요?',
    questionTranslation: 'Who is in the house?',
    answer: '엄마가 집에 있어요.',
    alternativeAnswers: ['집에 엄마가 있어요.'],
    answerTranslation: 'My mother is in the house.',    items: [
      { id: '1', content: '엄마', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '2', content: '가', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '3', content: '집', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '4', content: '에', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '5', content: '있어요.' },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 26,
    question: '회사에 누가 있어요?',
    questionTranslation: 'Who is at work?',
    answer: '아빠가 회사에 있어요.',
    alternativeAnswers: ['회사에 아빠가 있어요.'],
    answerTranslation: 'My father is at work.',    items: [
      { id: '1', content: '아빠', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '2', content: '가', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '3', content: '회사', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '4', content: '에', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '5', content: '있어요.' },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 27,
    question: '식당에 누가 있어요?',
    questionTranslation: 'Who is in the restaurant?',
    answer: '요리사가 식당에 있어요.',
    alternativeAnswers: ['식당에 요리사가 있어요.'],
    answerTranslation: 'A chef is in the restaurant.',    items: [
      { id: '1', content: '요리사', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '2', content: '가', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '3', content: '식당', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '4', content: '에', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '5', content: '있어요.' },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 28,
    question: '카페에 누가 있어요?',
    questionTranslation: 'Who is in the cafe?',
    answer: '오빠가 카페에 있어요.',
    alternativeAnswers: ['카페에 오빠가 있어요.'],
    answerTranslation: 'My brother is in the cafe.',    items: [
      { id: '1', content: '오빠', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '2', content: '가', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '3', content: '카페', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '4', content: '에', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '5', content: '있어요.' },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 29,
    question: '병원에 누가 있어요?',
    questionTranslation: 'Who is in the hospital?',
    answer: '가수가 병원에 있어요.',
    alternativeAnswers: ['병원에 가수가 있어요.'],
    answerTranslation: 'A singer is in the hospital.',    items: [
      { id: '1', content: '가수', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '2', content: '가', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '3', content: '병원', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '4', content: '에', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '5', content: '있어요.' },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 30,
    question: '영화관에 누가 있어요?',
    questionTranslation: 'Who is in the movie theater?',
    answer: '배우가 영화관에 있어요.',
    alternativeAnswers: ['영화관에 배우가 있어요.'],
    answerTranslation: 'An actor is in the movie theater.',    items: [
      { id: '1', content: '배우', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '2', content: '가', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '3', content: '영화관', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '4', content: '에', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '5', content: '있어요.' },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 31,
    question: '교실에 선생님이 있어요?',
    questionTranslation: 'Is a teacher in the classroom?',
    answer: '선생님이 교실에 없어요.',
    alternativeAnswers: ['교실에 선생님이 없어요.'],
    answerTranslation: 'A teacher is not in the classroom.',    items: [
      { id: '1', content: '선생님', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '2', content: '이', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '3', content: '교실', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '4', content: '에', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '5', content: '없어요.' },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 32,
    question: '학교에 학생이 있어요?',
    questionTranslation: 'Are students in school?',
    answer: '학생이 학교에 없어요.',
    alternativeAnswers: ['학교에 학생이 없어요.'],
    answerTranslation: 'A student is not in school.',    items: [
      { id: '1', content: '학생', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '2', content: '이', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '3', content: '학교', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '4', content: '에', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '5', content: '없어요.' },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 33,
    question: '도서관에 언니가 있어요?',
    questionTranslation: 'Is my sister in the library?',
    answer: '언니가 도서관에 없어요.',
    alternativeAnswers: ['도서관에 언니가 없어요.'],
    answerTranslation: 'My sister is not in the library.',    items: [
      { id: '1', content: '언니', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '2', content: '가', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '3', content: '도서관', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '4', content: '에', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '5', content: '없어요.' },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 34,
    question: '화장실에 친구가 있어요?',
    questionTranslation: 'Is my friend in the bathroom?',
    answer: '친구가 화장실에 없어요.',
    alternativeAnswers: ['화장실에 친구가 없어요.'],
    answerTranslation: 'My friend is not in the bathroom.',    items: [
      { id: '1', content: '친구', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '2', content: '가', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '3', content: '화장실', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '4', content: '에', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '5', content: '없어요.' },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 35,
    question: '집에 엄마가 있어요?',
    questionTranslation: 'Is my mother in the house?',
    answer: '엄마가 집에 없어요.',
    alternativeAnswers: ['집에 엄마가 없어요.'],
    answerTranslation: 'My mother is not in the house.',    items: [
      { id: '1', content: '엄마', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '2', content: '가', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '3', content: '집', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '4', content: '에', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '5', content: '없어요.' },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 36,
    question: '회사에 아빠가 있어요?',
    questionTranslation: 'Is my father at work?',
    answer: '아빠가 회사에 없어요.',
    alternativeAnswers: ['회사에 아빠가 없어요.'],
    answerTranslation: 'My father is not at work.',    items: [
      { id: '1', content: '아빠', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '2', content: '가', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '3', content: '회사', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '4', content: '에', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '5', content: '없어요.' },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 37,
    question: '식당에 요리사가 있어요?',
    questionTranslation: 'Is a chef in the restaurant?',
    answer: '요리사가 식당에 없어요.',
    alternativeAnswers: ['식당에 요리사가 없어요.'],
    answerTranslation: 'A chef is not in the restaurant.',    items: [
      { id: '1', content: '요리사', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '2', content: '가', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '3', content: '식당', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '4', content: '에', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '5', content: '없어요.' },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 38,
    question: '카페에 오빠가 있어요?',
    questionTranslation: 'Is my brother in the cafe?',
    answer: '오빠가 카페에 없어요.',
    alternativeAnswers: ['카페에 오빠가 없어요.'],
    answerTranslation: 'My brother is not in the cafe.',    items: [
      { id: '1', content: '오빠', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '2', content: '가', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '3', content: '카페', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '4', content: '에', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '5', content: '없어요.' },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 39,
    question: '병원에 가수가 있어요?',
    questionTranslation: 'Is a singer in the hospital?',
    answer: '가수가 병원에 없어요.',
    alternativeAnswers: ['병원에 가수가 없어요.'],
    answerTranslation: 'A singer is not in the hospital.',    items: [
      { id: '1', content: '가수', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '2', content: '가', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '3', content: '병원', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '4', content: '에', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '5', content: '없어요.' },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 40,
    question: '영화관에 배우가 있어요?',
    questionTranslation: 'Is an actor in the movie theater?',
    answer: '배우가 영화관에 없어요.',
    alternativeAnswers: ['영화관에 배우가 없어요.'],
    answerTranslation: 'An actor is not in the movie theater.',    items: [
      { id: '1', content: '배우', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '2', content: '가', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '3', content: '영화관', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '4', content: '에', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '5', content: '없어요.' },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 41,
    question: '집에 뭐가 있어요?',
    questionTranslation: 'What is there in the house?',
    answer: '집에 라면이 있어요.',
    alternativeAnswers: ['라면이 집에 있어요.'],
    answerTranslation: 'There is ramyeon in the house.',    items: [
      { id: '1', content: '라면', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '2', content: '이', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '3', content: '집', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '4', content: '에', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '5', content: '있어요.' },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 42,
    question: '집에 뭐가 있어요?',
    questionTranslation: 'What is there in the house?',
    answer: '집에 우유가 있어요.',
    alternativeAnswers: ['우유가 집에 있어요.'],
    answerTranslation: 'There is milk in the house.',    items: [
      { id: '1', content: '우유', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '2', content: '가', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '3', content: '집', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '4', content: '에', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '5', content: '있어요.' },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 43,
    question: '식당에 뭐가 있어요?',
    questionTranslation: 'What is there in the restaurant?',
    answer: '식당에 맥주가 있어요.',
    alternativeAnswers: ['맥주가 식당에 있어요.'],
    answerTranslation: 'There is beer in the restaurant.',    items: [
      { id: '1', content: '맥주', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '2', content: '가', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '3', content: '식당', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '4', content: '에', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '5', content: '있어요.' },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 44,
    question: '집에 뭐가 있어요?',
    questionTranslation: 'What is there in the house?',
    answer: '집에 사과가 있어요.',
    alternativeAnswers: ['사과가 집에 있어요.'],
    answerTranslation: 'There is apple in the house.',    items: [
      { id: '1', content: '사과', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '2', content: '가', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '3', content: '집', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '4', content: '에', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '5', content: '있어요.' },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 45,
    question: '집에 뭐가 있어요?',
    questionTranslation: 'What is there in the house?',
    answer: '집에 바나나가 있어요.',
    alternativeAnswers: ['바나나가 집에 있어요.'],
    answerTranslation: 'There is banana in the house.',    items: [
      { id: '1', content: '바나나', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '2', content: '가가', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '3', content: '집', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '4', content: '에', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '5', content: '있어요.' },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 46,
    question: '집에 뭐가 있어요?',
    questionTranslation: 'What is there in the house?',
    answer: '집에 포도가 있어요.',
    alternativeAnswers: ['포도가 집에 있어요.'],
    answerTranslation: 'There is grape in the house.',    items: [
      { id: '1', content: '포도', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '2', content: '가', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '3', content: '집', combineWithNext: true },
      { id: '4', content: '에', combineWithNext: false },
      { id: '5', content: '있어요.' },
    ],
  },
];

export const existenceQuestions = addGrammarName(questions, 'existence');
